Railway Labor Executives' Association Records 5484
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II: Office Files, 1954-1959
  - Legislation: General [folder 3 of 5], 1958 (Box 49, Folder 4c)
  - Legislation: General [folder 4 of 5], 1958 (Box 49, Folder 4d)
  - Legislation: General [folder 5 of 5], 1958 (Box 49, Folder 4e)
  - Legislation: General [folder 1 of 7], 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5a)
  - Legislation: General [folder 2 of 7], 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5b)
  - Legislation: General [folder 3 of 7], 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5c)
  - Legislation: General [folder 4 of 7], 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5d)
  - Legislation: General [folder 5 of 7], 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5e)
  - Legislation: General [folder 6 of 7], 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5f)
  - Legislation: General [folder 7 of 7], 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5g)
  - Legislation: General [folder 1 of 4], 1956 (Box 50, Folder 1a)
  - Legislation: General [folder 2 of 4], 1956 (Box 50, Folder 1b)
  - Legislation: General [folder 3 of 4], 1956 (Box 50, Folder 1c)
  - Legislation: General [folder 4 of 4], 1956 (Box 50, Folder 1d)
  - Legislation: General [folder 1 of 4], 1955 (Box 50, Folder 2a)
  - Legislation: General [folder 2 of 4], 1955 (Box 50, Folder 2b)
  - Legislation: General [folder 3 of 4], 1955 (Box 50, Folder 2c)
  - Legislation: General [folder 4 of 4], 1955 (Box 50, Folder 2d)
  - Legislation: General [folder 1 of 2], 1955-1956 (Box 50, Folder 3a)
  - Legislation: General [folder 2 of 2], 1955-1956 (Box 50, Folder 3b)
  - Legislation: Postal Pay, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: General [folder 1 of 2], 1954 (Box 50, Folder 5a)
  - Legislation: General [folder 2 of 2], 1954 (Box 50, Folder 5b)
  - Legislation: Appropriation Bills, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Attorneys Charging Lien Bill S.2456, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Federal Liability Act, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Federal Employers Liability Act, 1956-1957 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Federal Employees Liability Act, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Federal Employers Liability Act, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Federal Employers Liability Act, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Hours of Service, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Hours of Service, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Hours of Service, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Hours of Service, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Hours of Service, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act, Amending of 1957 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 18a)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act, Amending of 1957 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 18b)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act, Amending of, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: General, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Correspondence with House of Representatives [folder 1 of 3], 1955 (Box 51, Folder 1a)
  - Legislation: Correspondence with House of Representatives [folder 2 of 3], 1955 (Box 51, Folder 1b)
  - Legislation: Correspondence with House of Representatives [folder 3 of 3], 1955 (Box 51, Folder 1c)
  - Legislation: Track Motor Car Operation Bill, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Track Motor Car Operation Bill, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Labor, Management Relations Act, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: National Labor Relations Act, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Railroad Safety, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Rules of Practice and Procedure Before Federal Agencies, S.17 McCarran, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Social Security, General, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Social Security, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Social Security, General, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Tidelands Oil, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Transportation, Senate Committee Investigation of Surface, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: State Legislation, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: State, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Cabinet Committee, Report on Transportation S. 1920 and H.R. 6141 [folder 1 of 2], 1956 (Box 51, Folder 17a)
  - Legislation: Cabinet Committee, Report on Transportation S. 1920 and H.R. 6141 [folder 2 of 2], 1956 (Box 51, Folder 17b)
  - Legislation: Lobbying, Regulation of, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Social Security, General [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 51, Folder 19a)
  - Legislation: Social Security, General [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 51, Folder 19b)
  - Legislation: Social Security, General, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Transportation, Senate Committee Investigation of Surface, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Transportation, Senate Committee Investigation of Surface, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: State Legislation [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 51, Folder 23a)
  - Legislation: State Legislation [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 51, Folder 23b)
    File marked "Temporary."
  - Legislation: State Legislation [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 51, Folder 24a)
  - Legislation: State Legislation [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 51, Folder 24b)
  - Legislation: Hearings on Railroad Situation [folder 1 of 3], 1958 (Box 51, Folder 25a)
  - Legislation: Hearings on Railroad Situation [folder 2 of 3], 1958 (Box 51, Folder 25b)
  - Legislation: Hearings on Railroad Situation [folder 3 of 3], 1958 (Box 51, Folder 25c)
  - Legislation: Hearings on Railroad Situation [folder 1 of 5], 1958 (Box 52, Folder 1a)
  - Legislation: Hearings on Railroad Situation [folder 2 of 5], 1958 (Box 52, Folder 1b)
  - Legislation: Hearings on Railroad Situation [folder 3 of 5], 1958 (Box 52, Folder 1c)
  - Legislation: Hearings on Railroad Situation [folder 4 of 5], 1958 (Box 52, Folder 1d)
  - Legislation: Hearings on Railroad Situation [folder 5 of 5], 1958 (Box 52, Folder 1e)
  - Other Organizations: General, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: General, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Other Organizations: General, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Other Organizations: General, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Other Organizations: General, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: Faricy Meeting, June 15 [folder 1 of 4], 1955 (Box 52, Folder 7a)
  - RLEA: Faricy Meeting, June 15 [folder 2 of 4], 1955 (Box 52, Folder 7b)
  - RLEA: Faricy Meeting, June 15 [folder 3 of 4], 1955 (Box 52, Folder 7c)
  - RLEA: Faricy Meeting, June 15 [folder 4 of 4], 1955 (Box 52, Folder 7d)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 52, Folder 18a)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 52, Folder 18b)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-CIO, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: AFL, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Other Organizations: AFL, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Other Organizations: AFL, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Other Organizations: News from the AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Other Organizations: Collective Bargaining Report, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Other Organizations: COPE, AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Other Organizations: Free Trade Union News, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Minutes, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Education News and Views, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: Economic Trends and Outlook, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Legislative Action Bulletin, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Legislative Action Bulletin, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Other Organizations: Labor's Economic Review, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: American National Red Cross, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: Carriers' Conference Committee, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of the Physically Handicapped, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: American National Red Cross, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations: American National Red Cross, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Other Organizations: American National Red Cross, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads, 1954-1955 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: Community Chests and Councils of America, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Other Organizations: Community Chests and Councils of America, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Other Organizations: Community Chests and Councils of America, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations: Federation for Railway Progress, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Other Organizations: Federation for Railway Progress, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Other Organizations: Federation for Railway Progress, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Other Organizations: Inter-American Confederation of Workers, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Other Organizations: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), Press Releases, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Other Organizations: ICFTU, News, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations: ICFTU, Radio Service, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Other Organizations: ICFTU, Spotlight, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Other Organizations: International Labor Office, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Other Organizations: National Coal Association, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Other Organizations: National Coal Association, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Other Organizations: National Coal Association, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Other Organizations: National Coal Association, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Other Organizations: National Coal Association, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Other Organizations: National Labor-Management Foundation, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Other Organizations: National Planning Association, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Other Organizations: National Planning Association, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Other Organizations: National Planning Association, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - Other Organizations: National Planning Association, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - Other Organizations: Resources for the Future, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Other Organizations: Resources for the Future (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - Other Organizations: Resources for the Future, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 63)
  - International Affairs: International Transit Workers' Federation, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 64)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 53, Folder 26a)
  - Other Organizations: Association of American Railroads [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 53, Folder 26b)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers' Federation (ITF), 1958 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers' Federation, Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 54, Folder 2a)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers' Federation, Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 54, Folder 2b)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation, Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1956 (Box 54, Folder 3a)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation, Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1956 (Box 54, Folder 3b)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Vienna Congress [folder 1 of 3], 1956 (Box 54, Folder 4a)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Vienna Congress [folder 2 of 3], 1956 (Box 54, Folder 4b)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Vienna Congress [folder 3 of 3], 1956 (Box 54, Folder 4c)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation, Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1953 (Box 54, Folder 5a)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation, Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1953 (Box 54, Folder 5b)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - International Affairs: Surkhee, SB, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - International Affairs: South American Labor Leaders, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - International Affairs: Indonesian Labor People, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - International Affairs: Eriksson, Karl Birger. Swedish Railwaymens' Union, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - International Affairs: Jason Reint Jr., 1952 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - International Affairs: German Visitors, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - International Affairs: Italian Trade Union Team, M8A-TA-45-128, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - International Affairs: Norwegian Visitors, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - International Affairs: French Railway Labor Delegations, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - International Affairs: Campbell, EST MUR, England, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - International Affairs: Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - International Affairs: Indian Trade Union Leaders, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - International Affairs: ITF Circulars, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Press Reports, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Minutes, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Congress [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 54, Folder 22a)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Congress [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 54, Folder 22b)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Jim Campbell (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - International Affairs: ITF Executive Committee, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - International Affairs: ITF Management Committee, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations: Railway Labor's Political League, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Other Organizations: Railway Labor's Political League, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Other Organizations: Railway Labor's Political League, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Other Organizations: Railway Labor's Political League, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for A National Trade Policy, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: Denver and Rio Grande [DRGW] Hospital Association, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Other Organizations: Union Pacific Hospital Association, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Cooperative Educational and Public Society [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 55, Folder 14a)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Cooperative Educational and Public Society [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 55, Folder 14b)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Cooperative Educational and Public Society [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 55, Folder 15a)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Cooperative Educational and Public Society [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 55, Folder 15b)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Cooperative Educational and Public Society, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Cooperative Educational and Publishing Society, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: Hospital Associations, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: Hospital Associations, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: Hospital Associations, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Other Organizations: Hospital Associations, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations: Pension Associations, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: Pension Associations, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations: Pension Associations, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Other Organizations: Pension Associations, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Other Organizations: Dual Organizations, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Other Organizations: Dual Organizations, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Other Organizations: Dual Organizations, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Other Organizations: Dual Organizations, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: Harvard University, Trade Union Program, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Other Organizations: Harvard University, Trade Union Program, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Other Organizations: American Brotherhood of Railroad Employees, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations: Harvard University, Trade Union Program, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Other Organizations: National Capital Democratic Club, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Other Organizations: National Capital Democratic Club, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Other Organizations: Brotherhood Tours (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations: National Railroad Museum, Incorporated, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Other Organizations: Teacher Appointments, 1955 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    Federal Labor Union Conference
  - Other Organizations: Cornell On-Campus Conference, 1955 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Other Organizations: Federal Labor Union Conference Handouts: Cornell University July 26-29, 1955 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - RLEA: Report of Counsel, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, General [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 56, Folder 2a)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, General [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 56, Folder 2b)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, General [folder 1 of 3], 1957 (Box 56, Folder 3a)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, General [folder 2 of 3], 1957 (Box 56, Folder 3b)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, General [folder 3 of 3], 1957 (Box 56, Folder 3c)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, General (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, General (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, General, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, American Train Dispatchers Association v. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, American Train Dispatchers Association v. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, MissouriKansasTexas Railroad (MKT) (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, MissouriKansasTexas Railroad (MKT) (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, MissouriKansasTexas Railroad (MKT), 1954 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, Louisville and Nashville Railroad (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - RLEA: Court Cases, Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - RLEA: Court Decisions, Supreme Court, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - RLEA: Court Decisions, Supreme Court, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - RLEA: Court Decisions, Supreme Court (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - RLEA: Court Decisions, Supreme Court, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - RLEA: Foreign Correspondence, General, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - RLEA: Foreign Correspondence, General (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - RLEA: Foreign Correspondence, General (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - RLEA: Foreign Correspondence, General, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - RLEA: Foreign Correspondence, General (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - RLEA: Passes, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - RLEA: Passes (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - RLEA: Passes, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - RLEA: Passes, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - RLEA: Passes, 1958 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 1 of 3], 1958 (Box 56, Folder 29a)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 2 of 3], 1958 (Box 56, Folder 29b)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 3 of 3], 1958 (Box 56, Folder 29c)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 1 of 2], 1956 (Box 57, Folder 1a)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 2 of 2], 1956 (Box 57, Folder 1b)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 1 of 3], 1955 (Box 57, Folder 4a)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 2 of 3], 1955 (Box 57, Folder 4b)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 3 of 3], 1955 (Box 57, Folder 4c)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 1 of 3], 1954 (Box 57, Folder 5a)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 2 of 3], 1954 (Box 57, Folder 5b)
  - RLEA: Rules Movement [folder 3 of 3], 1954 (Box 57, Folder 5c)
  - RLEA: Committee for Health, Safety, and Convenience of Employees, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: Rules, Hiring Practices, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - RLEA: Committee on Facilities (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - RLEA: Cancelling Operating Contracts with Pullman Companies, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - RLEA: MissouriKansasTexas Railroad (MKT), 1958 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - RLEA: Southern Rules Movement [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 57, Folder 11a)
  - RLEA: Southern Rules Movement [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 57, Folder 11b)
  - RLEA; 1958 Rules Movement [folder 1 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 12a)
  - RLEA: 1958 Rules Movement [folder 2 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 12b)
  - RLEA: 1958 Rules Movement, Chicago and North Western System [folder 1 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 13a)
  - RLEA: 1958 Rules, Chicago and North Western System [folder 2 of 2] (Box 57, Folder 13b)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 58, Folder 1a)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 58, Folder 1b)
  - RLEA: Wages, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 1 of 3], 1954 (Box 58, Folder 3a)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 2 of 3], 1954 (Box 58, Folder 3b)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 3 of 3], 1954 (Box 58, Folder 3c)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 1 of 3], 1956 (Box 58, Folder 4a)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 2 of 3], 1956 (Box 58, Folder 4b)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 3 of 3], 1956 (Box 58, Folder 4c)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 1 of 3], 1955 (Box 58, Folder 5a)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 2 of 3], 1955 (Box 58, Folder 5b)
  - RLEA: Union Shop [folder 3 of 3], 1955 (Box 58, Folder 5c)
  - RLEA: Union Shop, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: Santa Fe Strike, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - RLEA: Santa Fe Strike [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 58, Folder 8a)